<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Wandz SDK</string>
    <string name="ai_features_title">AI Features</string>
    <string name="predictions_title">Predictions</string>
    <string name="audiences_title">Audiences</string>
    <string name="events_title">Events</string>
    <string name="affinities_title">Affinities</string>
    <string name="sample_actions">Sample Actions</string>
    <string name="show_interaction">Show Interaction</string>
    <string name="search_hint">Type to get adaptive suggestions</string>
    <string name="splash_text">Mobile SDK Demo App</string>
    <string name="wandz_ai">wandz.ai</string>
    <string name="all_rights">All rights reserved</string>
    <string name="adaptive_search">Adaptive Search</string>
    <string name="adaptive_search_action">See it in action</string>
    <string name="about_adaptive_search_title">About Adaptive Search</string>
    <string name="adaptive_search_description">Adaptive Search is a feature that helps users find what they are looking for by providing suggestions as they type. It uses machine learning to predict the user\'s intent and show relevant results.</string>
    <string name="interactions">Interactions</string>
    <string name="interactions_action">See it in action</string>
    <string name="about_interactions_title">About Interactions</string>
    <string name="interactions_description">Interactions is a feature that helps users engage with your app by providing suggestions based on their behavior. Deliver personalized, interactive promotions and messaging by leveraging real-time affinity detection, inferring visitor intent, and predicting their next action before they abandon.</string>
    <string name="sections">Sections</string>
    <string name="sections_action">Report Section change</string>
    <string name="about_sections_title">About section change Events</string>
    <string name="sections_description">Sections is a feature that helps you track user engagement by reporting section change events. It provides insights into how users interact with your app, which section they visit most frequently, and how long they spend on each section. Once a section was reported the Page Count will increase automatically, AI features that are calculated per page will be recalculated &amp; predictions will be recalculated as well. if "Order Confirmation" is reported the "purchased" ai feature will be flagged automatically. The preferred way of reporting consists of Section, description &amp; the current activity</string>
    <string name="events">Events</string>
    <string name="events_action">Learn how to fire events</string>
    <string name="about_events_title">About Events</string>
    <string name="events_description">Events is a feature that helps you track user actions by firing events (out of the box &amp; custom). It allows you to monitor user interactions, such as button clicks, form submissions, and other important actions, to gain insights into user behavior and improve your app. Additionally Wandz uses this data to improve its predictions.</string>
    <string name="affinities">Affinities</string>
    <string name="affinities_action">User affinities API</string>
    <string name="about_affinities_title">About Affinities</string>
    <string name="affinities_description">Affinities is a feature that helps you understand user preferences by providing insights into their interests, behaviors, and interactions with your app. It allows you to segment users based on their affinities and target them with personalized content, promotions, and recommendations. Once a user is detected as having an affinity, the user will continue to be associated with the affinity for 90 days. Additionally Wandz uses this data to improve its predictions.</string>
    <string name="fire">Fire</string>
    <string name="or">- OR -</string>
    <string name="reported_events">Reported Events</string>
    <string name="affinities_mock">As users navigate an e-commerce application, their preferences become clear through interactions with specific colors, such as blue or green, across multiple categories like shoes, jackets, or accessories. At the same time, their browsing patterns reveal an affinity for brands like Nike, Gucci, or Apple, helping tailor their shopping experience to their unique tastes.</string>
    <string name="scan_for_affinities">Scan for Affinities</string>
    <string name="affinities_reported">Affinities Reported</string>
    <string name="data">Raw Data</string>
    <string name="data_action">See raw data</string>
    <string name="custom_event_hint">Fire custom event</string>
</resources>