<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Wandz SDK</string>
    <string name="ai_features_title">AI Features</string>
    <string name="predictions_title">Predictions</string>
    <string name="audiences_title">Audiences</string>
    <string name="events_title">Events</string>
    <string name="affinities_title">Affinities</string>
    <string name="sample_actions">Sample Actions</string>
    <string name="show_interaction">Show Interaction</string>
    <string name="search_hint">Type to get adaptive suggestions</string>
    <string name="splash_text">Mobile SDK Demo App</string>
    <string name="wandz_ai">wandz.ai</string>
    <string name="all_rights">All rights reserved</string>
    <string name="adaptive_search">Adaptive Search</string>
    <string name="adaptive_search_action">See it in action</string>
    <string name="about_adaptive_search_title">About Adaptive Search</string>
    <string name="adaptive_search_description">Wandz.ai’s Adaptive Search enriches traditional search by layering real-time intelligence on top of existing functionality without disrupting it. It works seamlessly alongside autocomplete, preserving the familiar search experience while enhancing it with in-session personalization. Powered by affinities detected during the current visit—such as color, brand, or style preferences—it adapts results dynamically for every user, including anonymous and first-time visitors. It does not rely on past behavior, making it privacy-compliant and instantly effective. The result is a smarter, more relevant search experience that boosts discovery and conversion across the entire customer base.</string>
    <string name="interactions">Interactions</string>
    <string name="interactions_action">See it in action</string>
    <string name="about_interactions_title">About Interactions</string>
    <string name="interactions_description">Wandz.ai’s Adaptive Interactions deliver real-time, personalized messages through overlays and pop-ups—but what makes them truly powerful is the intelligence behind them. Instead of relying on static rules, segments, or historical data, they use Wandz.ai’s in-session AI to detect affinities, predict intent, and respond to visitor behavior in the moment. Whether someone is new, anonymous, or mid-journey, Adaptive Interactions identifies what matters—like price sensitivity, product interest, or exit intent—and triggers the right message at the right time. The key is Wandz.ai’s underlying real-time data and prediction layers, which enable teams to set up and manage these interactions without code. It’s a seamless way to turn passive visitors into active customers—without disrupting the experience or depending on part behavior.</string>
    <string name="sections">Sections</string>
    <string name="sections_action">Report Section change</string>
    <string name="about_sections_title">About section change Events</string>
    <string name="sections_description">Wandz.ai’s Automatic Section Mapping is a core capability that powers many of our real-time features by understanding your app structure—automatically. Instead of requiring manual tagging or engineering setup, Wandz.ai scans your app to detect and classify key sections like the homepage, category views, product detail screens, cart, checkout, and more. Using advanced pattern recognition and real-time analysis, it identifies the structure and intent of each screen as users navigate, even if the app has custom layouts or dynamic routes. This automatic mapping enables Wandz.ai to understand the customer journey from the very first session, in real time and at scale. It fuels features like Adaptive Search, Adaptive Interactions, and Flow Analytics by providing instant context—what the visitor is seeing, where they are in the funnel, and what matters most right now. It’s entirely no-code, privacy-compliant, and works out of the box, dramatically accelerating time to value while removing friction for product and data teams.</string>
    <string name="events">Events</string>
    <string name="events_action">Learn how to fire events</string>
    <string name="about_events_title">About Events</string>
    <string name="events_description">Wandz.ai’s Event Detection gives you real-time visibility into how users interact with your app—capturing key behaviors like product views, add-to-carts, scrolls, checkouts, and more, as they happen in-session. No manual tagging, no predefined tracking plans required. The system understands user actions across dynamic and custom app layouts, even for anonymous visitors. What makes this powerful is what comes next: once events are detected, you can use them to instantly build audiences, trigger personalized experiences, and launch real-time interactions—all without writing a single line of code. Whether it’s targeting users who viewed multiple products but didn’t convert or engaging high-intent shoppers mid-session, Wandz.ai lets business teams turn behavioral signals into action quickly.</string>
    <string name="affinities">Affinities</string>
    <string name="affinities_action">User affinities API</string>
    <string name="about_affinities_title">About Affinities</string>
    <string name="affinities_description">Wandz.ai’s Affinity Detection uncovers what each visitor cares about—right now—by analyzing in-session behavior in real time. Without relying on past data or user IDs, it identifies preferences like favorite brands, colors, categories, price sensitivity, and more. Information is gathered from the moment a user starts interacting with your app. These affinities are continuously updated as the session evolves, allowing you to understand intent and interests with high precision—even for anonymous or first-time users. Once detected, affinities become powerful building blocks you can use to personalize experiences, tailor search results, trigger adaptive interactions, and build dynamic audiences—all without code. Wandz.ai’s real-time affinity detection brings intelligence to every touchpoint, making your app feel instantly more relevant and responsive to each visitor.</string>
    <string name="fire">Fire</string>
    <string name="or">- OR -</string>
    <string name="reported_events">Reported Events</string>
    <string name="affinities_mock">As users navigate an e-commerce application, their preferences become clear through interactions with specific colors, such as blue or green, across multiple categories like shoes, jackets, or accessories. At the same time, their browsing patterns reveal an affinity for brands like Nike, Gucci, or Apple, helping tailor their shopping experience to their unique tastes.</string>
    <string name="scan_for_affinities">Scan for Affinities</string>
    <string name="affinities_reported">Affinities Reported</string>
    <string name="data">Raw Data</string>
    <string name="data_action">See raw data</string>
    <string name="custom_event_hint">Fire custom event</string>
    <string name="custom_section_hint">Fire custom section</string>
</resources>